check it out bro that guy over there is
trying to call The Suicide Prevention
Hotline see if you can intercept his
call and make him want to kill himself
even more okay that would be
hilarious welcome to the suicide hotline
we're so happy you
called because asking for help is a sign
of strength I want you to know that
you're not alone in this I may not
understand exactly how you feel but I
care about you and want to help what's
the hold up this better not be one of
your prank calls again you
[__] why won't my call go through I'm
seconds away from suicide right now I
knew it nobody cares about me if I don't
get through and have an emotional
conversation with someone right now I'm
going to kill myself and the blood will
be on their hands bro hang up this place
just turned into anavan and I ain't
taking the heat for this [__] you know
they say approximately one or two people
die every second on Earth so we are
going to stay on this call for exactly
20 seconds so you can feel the weight of
like 36 people who died in that short
period of time it's okay bro maybe he
won't
actually it's okay bro he was probably
going to do it anyway besides the only
ones who use Suicide Prevention are
basically a lost cause hello Suicide
Hotline sure I'll hold okay Sonia did
you want garlic butter sauce or marinara
all of them I demand the
sauce seems like Sonic is over there
with his green brother waiting to stuff
his goola with a pizza pie brilliant
then we made it in time to save that fat
Hedgehog ass y it would have been bad if
zanaa got to him before us rightly o co-
Warriors you're right odd I agree if we
can avoid unnecessary Bloodshed and
death I think we should act accordingly
did I say you could talk [__] no Jeremy
then stop it okay
Jeremy who the hell are you guys
supposed to be some larpers or some [__]
show some respect brussel sprout we're
the leoo Warriors leoo Warriors is that
an after school fan club we work in
secret to protect our planet from the
likes of zanah I'm Jeremy this is all
Rick and my [__] now give your things
Zen is coming here and he's planning on
[__] killing you and take over the
world but how did this Anna guy find me
it was the Pizza Hut app on your phone
he hacked into it to find out the time
and place you would be at to pick up
your 16-in meat lovers Pizza
that's it I'm [__] out of here see
you at home brother if you
survive [__] he's already here fly manic
fly it's been a while Leo Warriors but
it's too late this Hedgehog's life is M
to
take [__] [__] anyone else want to try
and run like a little [__] baby jemy we
should flee now and figure out a plan
later shut it paint brush head we G
fight this out it was you who said we
need to keep the secrets of Loko hidden
from public that was before he called me
a [__] need I remind you odd what
happened the last time AO Warrior spoke
back to
[Music]
me oh Rick watch out there's a monster
on your right
I see it Einstein thanks for watching my
CT I bet you enjoy the
[Music]
view well that's all of them should we
head back to school for lunch sorry you
me Jeremy said he wants us to explore a
little bit longer so we can collect more
data on henna still but we've been here
4 hours and I hear they're serving
meatballs and gravy in the lunchroom
today I say we leave anyway I mean what
is that four eyes going to do fight us
we're the [__] Loko Warriors
[__] destined to battle Zana he's just
the dweeb who runs the master computer
you're right anyone can do his job did
you just talk about me guess I'll just
have to remind you who the one with the
real power
is youi no Yi
what the [__] where did Yumi go she's
[__] gone [__] erased by Jeremy and
thrown into the digital sea forever
curse you Jeremy have you gone mad with
power why have you done this you've
changed Jeremy you have
[Music]
changed H your small
hand ride along with you it' be a funner
thing to do than well look who it is if
it isn't yumi's murderer have you come
to dematerialize us next you power
hungry weirdo son of a [__] be quiet I
dematerialized her because she was
annoying me and I can do the same to you
if I want so stop making me feel bad
that [__] got what she deserves and you
know it you need to lose the attitude
ice Ty I'm starting to think that this
battle with Zena is getting to your
head you would do well to remember who
really holds the power you Rick only I
can use the superc computer you L are
merely my funs I don't necessarily need
you but you however need me am I wrong
no then say it you're not wrong I know I
am not but you are you are very wrong
your Rick K me and I are going to the
cafeteria for me balls and baby do you
want to come with sure just let me go
put my school [__] away and then we can
dine on those
[Music]
balls Jeremy you're back where's Yumi I
noticed she didn't come back from lioko
today it was a bad
trip oh dear do you want to talk about
it there's nothing to talk about because
youi is dead you virtual [__] now
microwave me some nachos with a slice of
American and
cheese
what she's [__] dead [__] and it
wasn't because of a surprise attack from
zna it was all me I kicked her [__]
butt because I heard her talking [__]
about me without after materializing
them
andoko now I'm about to head to the
cafetera for some [__] meatballs and
gravy meatballs and gravy I think I'll
join you no need cuz the only meatballs
you're getting tonight are these ones
which
[Music]
while you so-called Warrior stand around
fighting amongst yourselves me and my
bro have a world that needs to be
[Music]
saved Sonic Sonic Manic Sonic isn't
waking up I think I think he's I think
he's
[Music]
dying he's going after Zenna all by
himself don't be a fool manic stop it's
not worth
[Music]
it Manic the he dog I already took your
brother out like a weak little poopy
baby [__] that filled his diaper to
the brim with steaming poop must I do
the very same to your Monster Energy
Drink colored butt shut up Zanna nobody
likes you code Le Yoko was [__]
canceled early because your show's
rating
[Music]
sucked ah you missed I wasn't aiming for
you I was aiming for the Street Lamp to
make it fall down on
you manic don't be a fool you're totally
outmatched here you must listen to us it
is understandable that you're angry
about your brother but throwing your
life away will achieve nothing Zanna is
by far the strongest enemy you have ever
fought this Zan person is powerful huh
then I suppose you would want someone on
your side that is actually strong and
not a weak little
[__] could it be it's really him it's
the Avatar The Last air bender that's
right it is me a the last air vender and
master of all four elements Now take me
to and I'll right the hell now so I can
use my air bending powers to shoot air
right up his ass and then I'll use my
air bending to pull it back out and then
make him eat that teir which will cause
him to fart again and look Prince Zuko
is here
too hello Zuko
here and watch out Zan is targeting
[Applause]
you
give me extra give me extra me
EXT
extra it's over Anna oh no with the leoo
Warriors Prince Zuko bang and manic they
really do make up the strongest team in
the world that's right and we're going
to use the power of teamwork to defeat
you
careful a Zanna can use his electrical
powers to take control of the wiring
under the ground you think that we'll
get the best of than one and only Avatar
I'll just have to take this fight to the
sky we'll see if you can get me after I
Fly Away using my air
glider [__] I forgot I can't fly because
my foot is wrapped up in the wires I'll
have to try something else
instead hey Z I'm the Avatar do you know
what that means you can use all the
elements
exactly Earth
fire
air
water hard by your powers combined I am
Captain Planet captain
son you have polluted this planet with
your evil ways long enough I'm going to
do what the Le Yoko Warriors never could
and put you in your [__] place you
smelly [__] sing for me
[__] the planet you can be one too
saving our planet is the thing to doing
anding is not the way here Captain
Planet
Avatar Captain Planet needs your
help dang there's a little bit of my
poop in this one guess you could call me
a poop bender
[Music]
haha I'll [__] kill you [__] this is
for Lazy Town
[__] what is he doing I believe Avatar
is using his air bending mixed with [__]
to choke
out yes Zanna may be evil but even bad
guys needs air to breath ha I don't even
have to try no one has ever survived my
Ancient Art of Air
B it's the Avatar's job to keep
everything in balance and with your
[__] demise balance is restored you
butt
wipe your job here is done Ang we thank
you for your service
manic I want to take you somewhere to
train over the weekend to train me but
I'm weak as [__] which is why I just
said I wanted to train you you [__]
[__] he needs stronger [__] to cover
his ass when the skillet gets hot and
trust me I know hot because I'm a fire
bender you were constantly told that you
were the weakest of the Hedgehog's
siblings and that you weren't born with
any special skills but that simply isn't
true but you saw how I was fighting zna
I would have died if it weren't for you
guys trust me you're a special manic
even more than your brother and sister I
noticed at the minute I laid eyes on you
that you are an Earth Bender an Earth
Bender why do you think when you summon
your drums you can make earthquakes and
[__] it's not the drums doing that it's
you it's from your
[Music]
heart come with me and I can teach you
how to harness the ancient art of Earth
binning even more so you won't have to
rely on
instruments manic are you really leaving
what about the golden Trio I have to As
Long As evil Reigns it will always come
after us I wasn't strong enough to do
anything today but things will be
different next time if that's where your
heart wants to take you then we won't
stop you go show those Earth venders
what a real Earth vendor is really made
of
[Music]
you are weak if you ever learn how to
move a single Rock come find me in my
dent and we shall discuss the next step
in your training that is if you haven't
given up by then you worth
[Music]
ler
dear Sonic and Sonia it's been eight
months and in that time I haven't even
moved a single
Rock but haitang tells me that if I keep
at a time I'd be able to roll a pebble
around in a couple of
decades Brazil's out I think it's time I
was honest with you you're not an Earth
Bender you just suck really bad I
thought you had to have some hidden
skill because you are so bad but you
don't please leave the Earth Kingdom
before I force you out
myself oh hell no [__] I came here so
you could teach me
earthbending but you have done nothing
for 8 months except to strip these for
the Fire Nation
Prince just know that when you meet your
ancestors in the great beyond that I
give you ample opportunity to walk
[Music]
away impossible I can Earth Bend I did
it I'm an Earth
Bender the strongest earthbender in the
world manicure back how was your
training with the Avatar and more
importantly do you want any Vienna
sausages you bet your ass sister you
looking at a certified earthbending
Master sick show us something you can do
with Earth bending yeah show us well I
kind of need to be outside to do it oh
never mind then Earth bending
sucks hey you guys who wants to go spit
on Zan's corpse you crazy son of a
[__] [__] I like the way you think
God let's [__] do it do it you mean
like do it as in you want to have sex
with me no I mean like go spit on sin
cors
[Applause]
zanna's not here he's gone he must have
escaped when we were eating
[Music]
pizza take you far away it's a fun thing
to say when I've never held your small
hand right along with you it' be a fun
thing to do then wake up you'll be here
to there's no time now to
explain oh
no sent on
Mission cuz I got a vision right now
little
angel bringing down your smile little
angel could it be a side little l sh
you're my beauty queen can't you break
the
cold get us out of here little angel
trapped inside this tream little
angel you're my prous thing little
angel keep me from the
pain
come before I go
sh
angel of
M angel of
M Angel
[Music]
the